How are you?
お元気ですか?
I'm fine.
元気です
You seem to be doing well.
元気そうですね
ERROR
ちょっと痩せたんじゃないですか?
Have you lost some weight?
ちょっと痩せましたか?
My legs are thin.
足は細い
Are you eating rice?
ご飯食べてる?
I'm eating a lot of rice.
ご飯めっちゃ食べてる
Are you eating a lot?
めっちゃ食べてる?
Are there any foods you've been into lately?
最近ハマってる食べ物とかある?
recently...
最近...
ERROR
カレー作ってます
picture?
え?
By myself?
自 分 で?
By yourself.
自分で
amazing.
すごい
Is that so?
そうなの?
ERROR
自炊するんだね
Cut the vegetables.
野菜切って
Kotokoto.
コトコト
ERROR
スパイスから?
Is it made from spices?
スパイスから作るの?
That's amazing.
すごいね
I'm particular about it.
こだわりが
Do you eat alone?
一人で食べるの?
Alone.
一人で
I'm feeding you.
食べさせてる
Isn't there someone you want to feed?
食べさせたい人がいるんじゃない?
The person you want to feed.
食べさせたい人
There might be.
いるかも
A little skippy.
ちょっとスキピー
There's Skippy.
スキピーがいる
I was able to skip.
スキピーできた
Look.
ほら
What kind of person are you?
どんな人なの?
My current job is...
今仕事は...
I agree.
そうだね
Great entertainment from the past.
昔すごい 芸能芸能
Did you do that?
やってたんだっけ?
Idol-like?
アイドル的な?
She's an idol.
ア イドルですね
Make it a company now.
今会社にして
Is it your senior?
先輩だ?
What do you think is good?
何がいいなと思ったの?
face.
顔
Handsome?
イケメン?
Is that so?
そうなの?
Do you wear a suit?
スーツ着たりするの?
He's wearing a suit.
スーツ着てるの
That's it.
そういう
It becomes a complex figure.
複体締める姿になる
Aren't you in love?
恋してない?
I haven't.
してない
Are you having sex?
エッチはしてる?
I haven't.
してないです
Haven't you?
してない?
It's better to do that.
したほうがいいよ
Skippy is here.
スキピーはいるし
Let's wait properly.
ちゃんと待っちゃおう
I'll usually wait longer than Skippy.
普通にスキピーより待っちゃおう
Let's wait for Skippy.
スキピーより待っちゃおう
It won't hurt any more.
それ以上が傷つかない
It doesn't work.
効かない
What should I do?
どう し よう
Are you strong-headed?
頭が強いですか?
誰?
There's Skippy.
スキピーがいる
My heart was broken.
心がバレちゃった
What kind of person are you?
どんな人?
You'll cause trouble.
トラブル起こすよ
Are you okay?
大丈夫?
Is it okay?
いいの?
A dog actress.
犬の女優とか
dangerous.
危ない
Let's stop.
やめましょう
Such a quick decision?
そんな速決?
速決?
Don't touch me.
手を出さないで
what are you doing?
何してるの?
That's what I was told.
って言われて
Let's temporarily change Skippy.
一時的にスキピー変えちゃおう
Just for now?
今だけ?
Only now.
今だけ
Awayoshi is permanent.
あわよくは永続的に
I'm saying it.
言わしてる
Become Skippy.
スキピーになってね
So, skippy now?
じゃ、もうスキピー?
Yeah.
うん
What can I do?
何してもいい?
You can do whatever you want.
何してもいい
Because I'm a skippy too.
俺もスキピーだから
I wonder why it's Skippy.
どうでスキピーだろうね
That's already the case, isn't it?
もうそういうことでしょ
That's how it looks.
格好がそうだよ
Mei-chan, let's go again.
メイちゃん、もう一回行っちゃおう
You can do whatever you want.
何してもいいんだよ
何してもいい
Skippy's body sound is really good.
スキピーの体サウンドめっちゃいい
If you're really into pants, why don't you serve me?
パンツメイチだったら サービスしちゃおうか
I didn't ask for it.
頼んないもんな
ERROR
飲みたくなってきちゃうでしょ
You'll want to drink it.
Can I drink it?
飲みていい?
Yeah.
うん
It's so beautiful.
めっちゃ綺麗だよ
Even the soles of her feet are cute.
足の裏まで可愛いね
It's an ordinary skirt.
イジュアルスカートだ
I'm putting on some pants.
もうちょっとパンツ入れてる
My eyes are clogged.
目づつまっちゃってる
Your pants are a great color.
パンツすごい色してるね
ERROR
こんな清掃な服ですけど
She's wearing surprisingly flashy underwear.
意外と派手な下着履いてる
Can you twist?
よれる?
It looks like it's looking good.
よっぽいよっぽい
It's not said much.
あんまり言われない
You won't be told.
言われないよ
ERROR
絶対いっぱい言われる気がする
It looks like it's looking good.
よっぽいよっぽいよ
Are you wearing naked clothes?
裸着着てるの?
I don't need a T-shirt.
Tシャツいらないから
Don't need a T-shirt?
Tシャツいらない?
I can see the colors.
色が見えちゃう
A very fancy brush.
すごい派手なブラシ
my favorite boo
大好きなブ
Rashi.
ラ シ
It's bright red.
真っ赤じゃん
I chose it.
選んだの
On the other hand, isn't it unnatural?
逆に不自然じゃない?
She's wearing underwear that looks like she has long hair.
すごい長髪的な下着履いてる
It's a joke.
つけつけじゃん
I can see it.
見えちゃってるよ
amazing.
すごい
It feels good to do both.
どっちもしても気持ちいい
She has really beautiful hair.
すごい綺麗な髪してる
It's a little damp.
ちょっと湿ってるね
Can I have candy here too?
ここも飴ていい?
When I say candy, I mean candy.
飴って言っても飴れるけど
what happened?
どうしたの?
Are you embarrassed?
恥ずかしい?
Because it's delicious.
美味しいからさ
Chikubi is so plump.
チクビすごいぷっくりしてる
copper
どう
Did you do it?
した の?
Are you embarrassed?
恥ずかしいの?
Because I can't see it yet.
まだ見えてないから
I feel so squishy.
すごいぷにぷに思う
I'll show you carefully.
じっかり見せる
I'm doing a little thing.
ちっちゃいもんこしてる
You can see all the colors.
全部色が見えちゃう
Looks like a butt.
お尻みたい
Something is sticking out.
なんかはみ出ちゃってる
That's bold.
大胆だね
It's okay to do anything.
何しても大丈夫
Look here.
こっち見て
That's bold.
大胆ですよ
I can see all of her butt holes.
お尻穴の穴も全部見えちゃってる
You're looking away.
目線反らせてんじゃん
Look closely in the eyes.
目をしっかり見て
It gives off a great scene.
すごい情景出してる
It looks good.
よく見えるし
Are you embarrassed?
恥ずかしいの?
It's opened.
開けられてる
See for yourself.
自分で見てみて
It looks really delicious.
本当に美味しそうだって
It's okay.
ちょっと大丈夫ね
I'll show you until I take a break.
私休憩まで見せる
Everything is seen.
全部見られてる
That's amazing.
すごいね
I can see your butt too.
尻も見えちゃってる
If I can flow something, I'll have a really nice voice.
なんか流れられたらめっちゃいい声出すし
Do you like it?
好きなの?
TRUE?
本当?
Get on top of my head.
俺の頭の上に乗ってよ
You like it, right?
好きなんだでしょ?
I wanted it so badly.
すっごい欲しかった
Look, it's sticking out.
見て、はみ出ちゃってる
Come here.
こっち来て
It's impossible.
無理だよ
Can you take a look here?
ここを眺めてくれる?
It feels amazing.
すごい気持ちいい
I can't stand it.
たまんないよ
I'm going to lick it.
舐めっこしちゃうよ
Is it okay?
いいの?
You have a headache, right?
頭痛いでしょ?
Open your eyes.
目を開けて
You got it right.
奥当たったね
Does it feel good?
気持ちいいの?
It feels good.
気持ちいいね
It feels so good.
気持ちよすぎる
It's the legs.
足だよ
amazing.
すごい
You went to the desk, right?
机上に行ったでしょ?
I want to see you cum from behind.
後ろから中出したの見たいんだけど
Another one
もう 一
I felt like fighting the round.
回 戦したくなっちゃった
I wish I could show you this much.
こんなに見せられたら
terrible.
やばい
I was surprised.
びっくりした
A dream is coming.
夢が来てる
Awesome.
すげえ
between each other
どうし
Good morning.
よう
I haven't touched it.
触 ってないんだ
It became beautiful.
綺麗になった
Yeah.
うん
It became beautiful.
綺麗になった
Because I did it after all.
やっぱりしちゃったから
difference.
さ
He said it was amazing.
すごい って言ってたから
amazing.
すごい
It feels good.
気持ちいいね
It stings and drips.
ヒ リヒリしたがれだしね
It feels so good.
気持ちよすぎる
good night.
おやすみ
can?
できる?
Can you do it?
できるかな?
Isn't it okay?
大丈夫 じゃないかな?
Shall I wash it?
洗ってあげようか
Because it feels so good.
気持ちよすぎるからさ
Is this going to happen?
このせわれる?
I need to clean it up.
綺麗にしないと
Because I keep it clean.
綺麗にしてるから
Even the last mouth is clean.
最後口でも綺麗にしてる
Do you mean put this in once?
一度これ入れてってこと?
Okay.
いいよ
Well then, shall I give you this one next time?
じゃあ今度こっちあげてやるか
Okay.
よっしゃよ
amazing.
すごい
Because it's an infinite loop.
無限ループだから
How many times do you repeat it?
何回繰り返すんだ
I'm sorry if I did this again.
またこうしちゃったらごめんね